Guide to the J. B. Matthews Papers, 1862-1986 and undated
J. B. Matthews papers 1862-1986 and undated
- Vertical Files Series, ca. 1920s-1980s Part III
  - International Council of Religious Education, 1945 (Folder 15)
  - International Disarmament Expedition of America, 1961 (Folder 16)
  - International Economic Research Bureau, undated (Folder 17)
  - International Federation of Resistance Fighters, 1955-1959 (Folder 18)
  - International Federation of War Veterans Organizations, 1951 (Folder 19)
  - International Federation of Women, 1945 (Folder 20)
  - International Film Foundation, Inc., undated (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union, 1946-1961 (Folder 2)
  - International Harvester, undated (Folder 3)
  - International Institute of Arts and Letters, 1961 (Folder 4)
  - International Juridical Association, 1929-1941 (Folder 5)
  - International Labor Conference, 1948 (Folder 6)
  - International Labor Defense, 1927-1946& undated (Folder 7-9)
  - International Labor Organization, 1953-1969 (Box 284, Folder 1-2)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1947 (Folder 3)
  - International Latex Corporation, 1944-1957 (Folder 4)
  - International League for the Rights of Man, 1949-1965 (Folder 5)
  - International League of Garment Worker's Union Trade Unionists for Peace, 1967 (Folder 6)
  - International Libertarians Group, 1937 (Folder 7)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU)
    - General Papers, 1949-1962 (Box 285, Folder 1-6)
    - General Papers, 1963-1969 (Box 286, Folder 1-4)
    - Clippings, 1949-1965 (Folder 5)
    - The Dispatches, 1955-1956 (Folder 6)
  - The Dispatches, 1957-1964 (Box 287, Folder 1-2)
  - International of Youth, 1935 (Folder 3)
  - International Olympic Committee, 1936-1952 (Folder 4)
  - International Organization of Journalists, 1957-1966 (Folder 5)
  - International Peace/Disarmament Directory, 1962-1963 (Folder 6)
  - International Press Conference, undated (Folder 7)
  - International Press Correspondence, 1928Issued in Vienna, Austria. (Folder 8)
  - International Publishers, 1930-1970 (Box 288, Folder 1-3)
  - International Relations, 1953 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - International Relations for Peace, undated (Folder 2)
  - International Rescue Committee, 1947-1961 (Folder 3)
  - International Research on Communist Techniques, 1951-1959 (Folder 4)
  - International Review, 1936-1941 (Folder 5)
  - International Review Service, 1957-1961 (Folder 6)
  - International Seaman's Club, 1930 (Folder 7)
  - International Services of Information Foundation, Inc., 1950-1964 (Folder 8)
  - International Socialist Party, 1970 (Folder 9)
  - International Socialist Review, 1957-1970 (Folder 10)
  - International Socialists, 1970 (Folder 11)
  - The International Society for Krishna Consciousness, 1966-1968 (Folder 12)
  - International Solidarity Committee, 1949 (Folder 13)
  - International Solidarity Committee to Aid Labor, Socialist and Democratic Anti-Fascists, 1947 (Folder 14)
  - International Student Conference at Prague, 1946 (Folder 15)
  - International Student Service, 1941 (Folder 16)
  - International Typographical Union, 1948 (Folder 17)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE) - Papers, 1949-1970 (Folder 18)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers
    - Papers, 1944-1967 (Box 290, Folder 1-6)
    - Papers, undated (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - The Mine-Mill Union, 1953-1960 (Folder 2-3)
  - International Union of Students (IUS)
    - General Papers, 1947-1958 (Folder 4-6)
    - General Papers, 1959-1972& undated (Box 292, Folder 1-2)
    - Broadsides (Posters), undated (Folder 3)
    - Periodicals: General, 1956-1971 (Folder 4)
    - News Service, 1958-1959 (Folder 5)
    - News Service, 1960-1972 (Box 293, Folder 1-4)
    - World Student News, 1949-1977& undated (Folder 5)
    - Young Film, 1957-1964 (Folder 6)
  - International Voluntary Service, 1960 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - International Women's Day, 1942-1946 (Folder 2)
  - International Women's Day Celebration, 1942 (Folder 3)
  - International Workers Order, 1930-1958& undated (Folder 4-6)
  - International Youth Commission, 1936 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - International Youth Federation for Freedom, 1965 (Folder 2)
  - International Youth Festival, 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Internationalism, undated (Folder 4)
  - Internationalist Perspective, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Interne, 1946-1950 (Folder 6)
  - Interpreting the Labor News, 1951-1954 (Folder 7)
  - Interprofessional Association for Social Insurance, 1934-1936 (Folder 8)
  - Interracial Press of America, undated (Folder 9)
  - Interracial Workshop, 1948 (Folder 10)
  - Interreligious Committee on Vietnam, 1965 (Folder 11)
  - Interreligious Foundation for a Community Organization, 1969 (Folder 12)
  - Intourist Bulletin, 1935-1972Issued by Intourist, Inc. (Folder 13)
  - Iowa Farmers Union, 1955-1961 (Folder 14)
  - Iowans for Peace in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 15)
  - Iranian Students Association, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - Lush-American Committee for the Election of O'Dwyer and Quill, 1945 (Folder 17)
  - The Iron Curtain, 1948-1950 (Folder 18)
  - Irv Rurki Defense Committee, 1966 (Folder 19)
  - Irving Place Theatre, 1941-1942 (Folder 20)
  - Isacson, Leo, 1948 (Folder 21)
  - Isbell, Harold J., undated (Folder 22)
  - Isbrandtsen, 1950 (Folder 23)
  - Islam in America, undated (Folder 24)
  - Israel, 1953-1955 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Israel Horizons
    - General Papers, 1948-1962 (Folder 2)
    - Periodical Issues, 1958-1962 (Folder 3-7)
  - Israel Speaks, 1949-1955 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Italian-American Civil Rights League, 1970-1973 (Folder 2)
  - Italian-American Labor Council, Inc., 1947 (Folder 3)
  - Italian Committee to Aid the Children of Spain, undated (Folder 4)
  - Italian Heritage Newsletter, 1973 (Folder 5)
  - Italy Today, 1945 (Folder 6)
  - Iushewitz, Morris, 1951 (Folder 7)
  - Izvestiya, 1947-1950 (Folder 8)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1968-1969 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, William, 1950-1952 (Folder 2)
  - Jaffe, Philip, 1951 (Folder 3)
  - Jagan, Cheddi, 1962-1968 (Folder 4)
  - Jamaica Book Center, 1962-1965 (Folder 5)
  - James E. Jackson Defense Committee, 1956 (Folder 6)
  - James Keller Defense Committee, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
  - The James Madison Constitutional Law Institute, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Jami' At Al Islam, Inc., 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Jane Addams Peace Association, 1960 (Folder 10)
  - Jane Kennedy-Beaver 55 Defense Committee, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Japan Council Against A & H Bombs, 1962-1968 (Folder 12)
  - Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc., 1952 (Folder 13)
  - Japan Letter, 1956-1957 (Folder 14)
  - Japan Peace for Vietnam! Committee, 1966 (Folder 15)
  - Japanese-American Citizens League, undated (Folder 16)
  - Japanese-American Committee for Democracy, 1944-1945 (Folder 17)
  - Javits, Jacob R., 1956 (Folder 18)
  - Jayvan Covington Defend Fund, 1963 (Folder 19)
  - The Jeannette Rankin Brigade, 1967-1968 (Folder 20)
  - Jednota, 1947 (Folder 21)
  - Jefferson Avenue Revolutionary Union Movement, undated (Folder 22)
  - Jefferson Bookshop, 1957-1970 (Folder 23)
- Vertical Files Series, ca. 1920s-1980s Part IV
  - Jefferson School of Social Science
    - General Papers, 1941-1959& undated (Box 299, Folder 1-3)
    - Jefferson School of Social Science, 1944-1960& undated (Folder 4-5)
    - Writings, 1930-1954 (Folder 6)
    - Writings, 1955-1956& undated (Box 300, Folder 1-3)
  - Jefferson Theater Workshop, undated (Folder 4)
  - Jehovah's Witnesses, 1938-1967 (Folder 5-6)
  - Jencks, Clinton E., 195? (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Jeremiah Stabler, M.D., Legal Aid Fund, 1965-1970& undated (Folder 2-3)
  - Jesse Gordon and Associates, 1953-1958 (Folder 4)
  - Jessup, Philip C., 1951 (Folder 5)
  - Jewish-American Board for Peace and Justice, Inc., 1951 (Folder 6)
  - Jewish Black Book Committee, undated (Folder 7)
  - Jewish Citizens Committee for Community Control, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Jewish Community Relations Council, 1966 (Folder 9)
  - Jewish Community for Russian War Relief, Inc., 1946 (Folder 10)
  - Jewish Currents, 1957-1966 (Folder 11-12)
  - Jewish Currents, 1967-1970& undated (Box 302, Folder 1-2)
  - Jewish Defense League, 1969-1970 (Folder 3)
  - The Jewish Fraternalist, 1948 (Folder 4)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1947-1957 (Folder 5)
  - Jewish Life, 1948-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Jewish Music Alliance, 1949-1955 (Folder 7)
  - Jewish Occupational Council, 1945 (Folder 8)
  - Jewish Peace Fellowship, 1951-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Jewish People's Committee, 1938-1945 (Folder 10)
  - Jewish People's Committee for United Action Against Fascism and Anti-Semitism, 1939-1941 (Folder 11)
  - Jewish Peoples Fraternal Order, 1946-1947 (Folder 12)
  - Jewish Peoples Philharmonic Chorus, 1958 (Folder 13)
  - The Jewish Survey, 1942 (Folder 14)
  - Jewish Theaters Behind the Iron Curtain, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Jewish Trade Union Defenders of the Alter-Ehrlich Executions, 1942 (Folder 16)
  - Jewish War Veterans of the U.S.A., 1965 (Folder 17)
  - The Jewish Young Folksingers, 1955 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Young Fraternalists, undated (Folder 2)
  - Jewish Youth Builder, 1952 (Folder 3)
  - Jim Hayes Defense Fund, 1969 (Folder 5)
  - Jo Ann Santiago Defense Committee, 1959-1960 (Folder 6)
  - Jobs for Veterans, 1973 (Folder 7)
  - Jobs or Income Now (J.O.I.N.), 1966 (Folder 8)
  - The Johannes Steel Report on World Affairs, 1946-1947 (Folder 9)
  - John Birch Society - Papers, 1959-1974& undated (Folder 10-12)
  - John Brown College, 1965-1966 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - John Brown Commemoration Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 2)
  - John Coughlan Defense Committee, 1948 (Folder 3)
  - John Dewey Society for the Study of Education and Culture, 1937-1939 (Folder 4)
  - John J. Abt Dinner Tribute, 1968 (Folder 5)
  - John J. Abt Testimonial Committee, 1960 (Folder 6)
  - John Noto Defense Committee, 1956 (Folder 7)
  - John Otto, 1954-1967 (Folder 8)
  - John Reed Clubs of the United States, 1930-1936 (Folder 9)
  - John Reed Society, 1949 (Folder 10)
  - Johnny Appleseed Patriotic Publications, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Johnson-Forest Group, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Hewlett, 1950 (Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Manning, 1957 (Folder 14)
  - Join, 1965-1966 (Folder 15)
  - Join Hands, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - Joint Action Group, 1946-1947 (Folder 17)
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1938-1967 (Folder 18-19)
  - Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Union, 1947-1962 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Joint Board Furriers Union, 1926 (Folder 2)
  - Joint Campaign for Political Refugees, 1948 (Folder 3)
  - Joint Committee Against Communism in New York, 1951-1953 (Folder 4)
  - Joint Committee for Trade Union Rights, 1940 (Folder 5)
  - Joint Committee of Czechoslovak Organizations, 1937 (Folder 6)
  - Joint Committee on Unemployment, 1932 (Folder 7)
  - Joint Committee to Aid the Herndon Defense, 1935 (Folder 8)
  - Joint Committee to Combat Anti-Semitism, 1949 (Folder 9)
  - Joint Committee to Secure A Fair Trial of the Trenton Six, 1951 (Folder 10)
  - Joint Conference Against Intervention in Greece and Turkey, 1947 (Folder 11)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Charitable and Philanthropic Agencies and Organizations, 1956 (Folder 12)
  - Joint Maritime Strike Committee, undated (Folder 13)
  - Joint Maritime Strike Committee of the Port of New York, undated (Folder 14)
  - Joint May Day Committee of New York, undated (Folder 15)
  - Joint Peace Committee for Nassau and Queens, 1965 (Folder 16)
  - Joint Self Defense Committee, 1956-1957 (Folder 17)
  - Joint United States-Mexico Trade Union Committee, undated (Folder 18)
  - Joint Veterans Council for Americanism, undated (Folder 19)
  - Jomo Freedom Renyatta House, 1966-1967 (Folder 20)
  - Jones, Edward, 1950 (Folder 21)
  - Jones, Leroi, 1964 (Folder 22)
  - Joseph F. Rehoe Trust Fund, 1961 (Folder 23)
  - Joseph North Testimonial Committee, 1958 (Folder 24)
  - Josephson, Leon, undated (Folder 25)
  - Journal of American Society to Defend Children, 1947-1965 (Folder 26)
  - Journal of International Affairs, 1957 (Folder 27)
  - Journal of Social Issues, 1947-1974 (Folder 28)
  - Juan Farinas Defense Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 29)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1946 (Folder 30)
  - Judson Ring Foundation, 1944 (Folder 31)
  - Judy's Magazine, 1949-1950Issued by Judy's Publishing Co. (Folder 32)
  - Jugendinternationale, 1934 (Folder 33)
  - The Julian Press, Inc., 1962 (Folder 34)
  - The Julius Rosenthal Memorial Committee for Aid to the Basque Refugee Children, 1937 (Folder 35)
  - July 23rd Defense Committee, 1969 (Folder 36)
  - Junta of Militant Organizations, 1969 (Folder 37)
  - Jurist, Irma, 1948 (Folder 38)
  - Justice for Pelley Committee, 1949 (Folder 39)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1961 (Folder 40)
  - Juvenile Delinquents, Russian, 1969 (Folder 41)
  - K.M.P.C., 1950 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Kahn, Albert E., 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Kahn, Arthur David, undated (Folder 3)
  - Kansas Institute of International Relations, 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Kaplan, J. M. Fund, Inc., 1964-1969 (Folder 5)
  - Karolyi, Catherine, undated (Folder 6)
  - Karpatsha, Rus, 1944-1948 (Folder 7)
  - Karr, David, undated (Folder 8)
  - Kasenkina, Oksana, 1949 (Folder 9)
  - Kasper, Frederich John, undated (Folder 10)
  - Kauffman, Joseph P., 1962 (Folder 11)
  - Kazin, Alfred, 1970 (Folder 12)
  - Keane, George, 1947 (Folder 13)
  - Keep America Free Council, Inc., 1954 (Folder 14)
  - Keep America Out of War Committee, 1938-1940 (Folder 15)
  - Keep Proportional Peoples Representation Rule, undated (Folder 16)
  - Kefauver Committee, 1951 (Folder 17)
  - Kellock, Katherine, 1936 (Folder 18)
  - Kennan, George, 1968 (Folder 19)
  - Kennedy Assassination Inquiry Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 20)
  - Kennedy, Edward Moore, 1969-1970 (Folder 21)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1970 (Box 307, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy, John F. Library for Minorities, 1969 (Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Robert, 1967-1968 (Folder 3)
  - Kennyatta, Charles, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Kensman, Karl, 1955 (Folder 5)
  - Kent Legal Defense Fund, 1970 (Folder 6)
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1937-1967 (Folder 7)
  - Kent State University, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Kentuckians Against RUAC, 1969 (Folder 9)
  - Kentuckians for Peace, 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Kentucky Conference on the War and the Draft, 1968 (Folder 11)
  - Kenyon, Dorothy, 1940s (Folder 12)
  - Keystone Foundation Inc., 1949 (Folder 13)
  - Khoklov, Niholai E., 1954-1957 (Folder 14)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita S., 1956-1964 (Folder 15)
  - Killian Defense Committee, 1959-1961 (Folder 16)
  - Kimn, Diamond, 1945-1962 (Folder 17)
  - Kimmel, George, 1950 (Folder 18)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1961-1970 (Folder 19)
  - King, Mrs. Martin Luther, 1960-1969 (Folder 20)
  - Kings County Committee, Communist Party, 1946 (Folder 21)
  - Kirk, Grayson, 1959 (Folder 22)
  - Klinefelter, Harry, 1951 (Folder 23)
  - Kluckton, Frank, 1969 (Folder 24)
  - Knauff, Ellen, Mrs., 1951 (Folder 25)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1946 (Folder 26)
  - Knights of the White Camellia, 1939 (Folder 27)
  - Knopf, Alfred, 1951-1967 (Folder 28)
  - Know the Truth, 1951 (Folder 29)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1937-1970& undated (Box 308, Folder 1-6)
  - Koinonia Farm, 1953-1961 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Konigsberg Legal Fund, 1956 (Folder 2)
  - Kophin, Andrew, 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Kord Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1965 (Folder 4)
  - Korea, 1951-1968 (Folder 5)
  - Korean Independence, 1945-1956 (Folder 6)
  - Korean Relief Inc., undated (Folder 7)
  - Kosygin, Aleksei, 1968 (Folder 8)
  - Kraber, Gerrit, 1952 (Folder 9)
  - Kraus, Sylvia, 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Krebs, Richard, 1951 (Folder 11)
  - Krishna Consciousness, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Krivitsky, Walter, 1939-1966 (Folder 13)
  - Ku Klux Klan
    - General Papers, 1921-1965 (Folder 14-16)
    - General Papers, 1966-1969& undated (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
    - Volumes, 1964-1967 (Folder 3-4)
  - Kutcher Civil Rights Committee, 1949 (Folder 5)
  - Kyles, Pugh, 1951 (Folder 6)
  - Labor, 1935-1938 (Box 311, Folder 1-2)
  - Labor Action, 1956 (Folder 3)
  - Labor Advisory Committee, 1951 (Folder 4)
  - Labor and Nation, 1947 (Folder 5)
  - Labor Arts, undated (Folder 6)
  - Labour Audit Bureau, undated (Folder 7)
  - Labor Commission, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Labour Committee for Amter, 1941 (Folder 9)
  - Labor Committee for Peace in Vietnam, 1966 (Folder 10)
  - Labor Committee to Combat German Rearmament, 1951 (Folder 11)
  - Labor Conference for Peace, 1951 (Folder 12)
  - Labor Day Mass Committee, 1952 (Folder 13)
  - Labor Defender, 1930-1933 (Folder 14)
  - Labor for Unity and Victory Committee, 1943 (Folder 15)
  - Labor Herald, 1947 (Folder 16)
  - Labor Law Journal, 1949 (Folder 17)
  - Labor League for Human Rights, 1942 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - The Labour Monthly, 1930 (Folder 2)
  - Labor Negro Vanguard Conference, 1961-1964 (Folder 3)
  - Labor News Digest, 1947 (Folder 4)
  - Labor Peace Action, 1950 (Folder 5)
  - Labor Press Committee, undated (Folder 6)
  - The Labor Press Reporter, 1946 (Folder 7)
  - Labor Research Association, 1934-1963 (Folder 8)
  - Labor Review, 1947 (Folder 9)
  - Labor Sports Federation, 1947 (Folder 10)
  - Labor Today, 1963-1969 (Folder 11)
  - Labor Union, 1947 (Folder 12)
  - Labor Unity, 1934-1935 (Folder 13)
  - Labor Vanguard, 1945 (Folder 14)
  - Labor Youth League (LYL)
    - General Papers, 1937-1956& undated (Box 313, Folder 1-2)
    - Government Documents, 1953-1956& undated (Folder 3-4)
  - Labor's Anti-Hitler Committee, undated (Folder 5)
  - Labor's Non-Partisan League, 1938-1945 (Folder 6)
  - Lachawana Railroad, 1948 (Folder 7)
  - Lader, Lawrence, 1948 (Folder 8)
  - La Farge, Oliver, 1954 (Folder 9)
  - Lafayette, Bernard, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - La Follette Committee, 1936-1952 (Folder 11)
  - Laidler, Harry, 1957-1970 (Folder 12)
  - Laisve. 1958-1960 (Folder 13)
  - Lamb, Edward, 1954 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Lamb, Helen, 1964 (Folder 2)
  - Lambert, Rarel, 1969 (Folder 3)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1951-19690 (Folder 4)
  - The Lance, 1947-1951 (Folder 5)
  - Lardner, Ring, 1953-1965 (Folder 6)
  - Larson, Orville, 1949 (Folder 7)
  - Lash, Joseph, 1942-1966 (Folder 8)
  - Lasher, Bruno, 1954 (Folder 9)
  - Lashi, Harold, 1955 (Folder 10)
  - Lasky, Richard, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Lasswell, Harold, 1954-1955 (Folder 12)
  - Last Harass, 1969 (Folder 13)
  - Lathrop, John, 1955 (Folder 14)
  - Latin America, 1958-1975 (Folder 15)
  - Latin America Defense Organization, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - Latin America Research Bureau, 1951-1974 (Folder 17)
  - Latin America Solidarity Organization, 1967 (Folder 18)
  - Latin America Today, 1951-1957 (Folder 19)
  - La Touche, John, 1947-1948 (Folder 20)
  - Lattimer, Ira, 1958 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - Lattimore Defense Fund, 1952-1957 (Folder 2)
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1943-1969 (Folder 3)
  - Lauchs, Iwing, 1960s (Folder 4)
  - Laurence, Paula, 1945 (Folder 5)
  - Laurents, Arthur, 1949 (Folder 6)
  - Lauter, Paul, 1960s (Folder 7)
  - Law Center for Constitutional Rights, 1967-1969 (Folder 8)
  - Law in Transition Quarterly, 1964 (Folder 9)
  - Lawrence, Alton, 1952 (Folder 10)
  - Lawrence, Appleton, 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Lawrence, Peter, 1949-1951 (Folder 12)
  - Laws, Clarence, 1965 (Folder 13)
  - Lawson, John, 1963 (Folder 14)
  - Lawson, Mark, 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Lawyers Against the War, 1969 (Folder 16)
  - Lawyers Committee on American Relations with Spain, 1939 (Folder 17)
  - Lawyers Committee to Keep the U.S. Out of War, 1940 (Folder 18)
  - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee, 1969 (Folder 19)
  - Lazarus, Simon, 1949-1957 (Folder 20)
  - Lazo, Mario, 1968-1970 (Folder 21)
  - Le Metro, 1969 (Folder 22)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1969 (Folder 23)
  - Leadership Foundation, 1966 (Folder 24)
  - League for Adult Education, 1942-1945 (Folder 25)
  - League for Cultural Freedom and Socialism, undated (Folder 26)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (LID) (Box 316)
    - General Papers, 1935-1970 (Folder 1-3)
    - Pamphlets and Volumes, 1938-1965 (Folder 4-6)
  - League for Mutual Aid, 1946-1956 (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - League of American Writers, 1943 (Folder 2)
  - League of Struggle for Negro Rights, undated (Folder 3)
  - League of Women Shoppers, 1943-1949 (Folder 4)
  - League of Women Voters, 1956-1964 (Folder 5)
  - Leake, Chauncey, 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Lear, Walter, 1948 (Folder 7)
  - Ledden, Carl, undated (Folder 8)
  - Lee, Canada, 1949-1952 (Folder 9)
  - Lee, Gypsy, Rose, 1950 (Folder 10)
  - Lee, Madeline, undated (Folder 11)
  - Lee, Michael J., 1950 (Folder 12)
  - Lee, Robert, 1962 (Folder 13)
  - Leeds, Oliver, undated (Folder 14)
  - Leeper, Robert, 1955 (Folder 15)
  - Lees, Robert, 1953 (Folder 16)
  - Leff, David, 1954-1955 (Folder 17)
  - Left Face, 1969-1970 (Folder 18)
  - Left Leaf, 1965 (Folder 19)
  - Left Review, 1935-1936 (Folder 20)
  - Legion-Anderson, 1966-1974 (Folder 21)
  - Legislation, 1956-1962 (Folder 22)
  - Legislative Assembly, 1949 (Folder 23)
  - Lehman, Herbert, 1954 (Folder 24)
  - Leigh, Robert, 1955 (Folder 25)
  - Leiper, Henry, Dr., 1939 (Folder 26)
  - Leland Stanford University, undated (Folder 27)
  - Lens, Sidney, 1967 (Folder 28)
  - Leo Potishman Foundation, undated (Folder 29)
  - Leonard, Thomas, Mrs., 1941 (Folder 30)
  - Lerman, Louis, 1957 (Folder 31)
  - Lerner, Herb, 1950 (Folder 32)
  - Lerner, Irving, 1955 (Folder 33)
  - Lerner, Max, 1953-1956 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - LeRoy, Gaylord, 1967 (Folder 2)
  - Leslie, Kenneth, 1944 (Folder 3)
  - LeSueur, Meridel, 1955 (Folder 4)
  - Let Freedom Ring, 1965 (Folder 5)
  - Lev, Ray, 1955 (Folder 6)
  - Levene, Sam, undated (Folder 7)
  - Levenson, Sam, undated (Folder 8)
  - Lever, Emil, 1923 (Folder 9)
  - Levering, Robert, 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Leviathan, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Levine, Estelle, undated (Folder 12)
  - Levine, Isaac, 1958 (Folder 13)
  - Levy, David, 1955 (Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Alfred, undated (Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Edward, 1957 (Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Fulton, 1948-1971 (Folder 17)
  - Lewis, John, 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, 1955 (Folder 19)
  - Ley, Willy, Dr., 1953 (Folder 20)
  - Liberal Citizens of Massachusetts, 1958-1962 (Folder 21)
  - The Liberal Papers, 1967 (Folder 22)
  - Liberal Party, 1944-1968 (Folder 23)
  - Liberal-Religous Fellowship, 1964 (Folder 24)
  - Liberal Survey, 1939 (Folder 25)
  - Liberalist Jacobinism versus Constitutionalism, 1956-1965 (Folder 26)
  - Liberate Yourself Now, 1969 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Liberated Church Press, 1969 (Folder 2)
  - Liberated Guardian Collective, 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Liberated Youth of Niles Township, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Liberation (Folder 5)
  - Liberation, 1956-1970 (Folder 6-9)
  - Liberation Committee for Africa, 1961-1962 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Liberation News Service - Papers, 1968-1970& undated (Folder 2-3)
  - Liberation Support Movement Information Center, undated (Folder 4)
  - Liberation University, 1968 (Folder 5)
  - Liberator, 1967-1970 (Folder 6)
  - Libertarian Committee for Freedom in Spain, undated (Folder 7)
  - Libertarian League, 1960-1966 (Folder 8)
  - Libertarian Press, 1957-1962 (Folder 9)
  - Libertarian Republican Alliance, 1976 (Folder 10)
  - Libertarian Socialist Committee, 1956-1957 (Folder 11)
  - Libertas, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Liberties Appeal Committee for Michigan-Smith Act Defendants, 1956-1957 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Liberty, 1970-1973 (Folder 2)
  - Liberty Amendment, 1964-1970 (Folder 3)
  - Liberty and Property, 1955-1959 (Folder 4)
  - Liberty Belles, undated (Folder 5)
  - Liberty Book Club Forum, 1959 (Folder 6)
  - Liberty Defense Union, 1918 (Folder 7)
  - Liberty House, 1967 (Folder 8)
  - Liberty Lobby, 1963-1975 (Folder 9)
  - Liberty (Prometheus Paperback) Book Club, 1951-1964 (Folder 10-11)
  - Librarians, 1969 (Folder 12)
  - Library for Intercultural Studies, 1959-1963 (Folder 13)